const sport = [
    {
        number: "1",
        question: "What is Usain Bolt’s 100m world record time?",
        answer: "9.58 seconds",
        hint: "Sub - 10 seconds"
    },
    {
        number: "2",
        question: "Which England footballer was famously never given a yellow card?",
        answer: "gary lineker",
        hint: "Appears in adverts for walkers crisps"
    },
    {
        number: "3",
        question: "How many world titles has Phil Talyor won in darts?",
        answer: "16",
        hint: "Between 14 and 18"
    },
    {
        number: "4",
        question: "Who is the only player to have scored in the Premier League, Championship, League 1, League 2, Conference, FA Cup, League Cup, Football League Trophy, FA Trophy, Champions League, Europa League, Scottish Premier League, Scottish Cup and Scottish League Cup?",
        answer: "gary hooper",
        hint: "Born 1988, Harlow"
    },
    {
        number: "5",
        question: "The LA Lakers and New York Knicks play which sport?",
        answer: "basketball",
        hint: "Typically played professionally on an indoor court"
    },
    {
        number: "6",
        question: "Katarina Johnson-Thompson is world champion in which sport?",
        answer: "heptathlon",
        hint: "This sport is combination of track and field, consisting of seven events"
    },
    {
        number: "7",
        question: "Which country did F1 legend Ayrton Senna come from?",
        answer: "brazil",
        hint: "The largest South American country"
    },
    {
        number: "8",
        question: "A penalty in football is taken how many yards away from the goal?",
        answer: "12 yards",
        hint: "Between 10 and 14 yards"
    },
    {
        number: "9",
        question: "Who holds the women's record for the 100m sprint?",
        answer: "florence griffith-joyner",
        hint: "Known as Flo-Jo"
    },
    {
        number: "10",
        question: "What club were West Ham United founded as?",
        answer: "thames ironworks",
        hint: "The Hammers symbolise these club"
    },
    {
        number: "11",
        question: "Who has scored the most Premier League hat-tricks?",
        answer: "sergio aguero",
        hint: "Argentine footballer"
    },
    {
        number: "12",
        question: "Who were Man Utd playing when Eric Cantona leaped into the crowd and kicked a fan?",
        answer: "crystal palace",
        hint: "Located in Selhurst, South London"
    },
    {
        number: "13",
        question: "In which sport do you wear a plastron?",
        answer: "fencing",
        hint: "Points are awarded in this sport by the sabre hitting the opponent"
    },
    {
        number: "14",
        question: "Which sport involves tucks and pikes?",
        answer: "diving",
        hint: "Tom Daley has two gold medals in this sport"
    },
    {
        number: "15",
        question: "Who is the Premier League’s all-time top scorer?",
        answer: "alan shearer",
        hint: "Currently a match of the day presenter"
    },
    {
        number: "16",
        question: "Jessica Ennis-Hill competed for Great Britain in which sport?",
        answer: "heptathlon",
        hint: "This sport is combination of track and field, consisting of seven events"
    },
    {
        number: "17",
        question: "England won the 2003 Rugby World Cup thanks to an iconic, last-gasp drop goal from Jonny Wilkinson. How many points did England score in that famous match?",
        answer: "20",
        hint: "Between 17 and 21"
    },
    {
        number: "18",
        question: "Which famous football manager once said: “I wouldn’t say I was the best manager in the business. But I was in the top one”?",
        answer: "bryan clough",
        hint: "Quoted to have said: They say Rome wasn't built in a day, but I wasn't on that particular job."
    },
    {
        number: "19",
        question: "How many F1 championships has Lewis Hamilton won?",
        answer: "6",
        hint: "Between 3 and 8"
    },
    {
        number: "20",
        question: " Chris Wilder helped guide Sheffield United from League One to the Premier League. In the Blades' League One title-winning season, how many points did they accumulate?",
        answer: "100",
        hint: "Between 94 and 112"
    }

];

export default sport;
